Good morning.
Wow.
There it is again.
You're so sweet to get lunch for all of us, until we all get lunch.
I guess the patience game has begun.
Until they get theirs.
Ta-da!
I won the sticker raffle!
Even the lovely Miss Angeleur!
Here's Hiyorin, right here.
Thank you very much!
I got a golden tan bento!
I'm so happy!
I'll draw one card.
No luck.
I see Akari a lot.
How nice
So kind.
Kurameki-chan got it.
Cookies in the member's color
Good morning.
Half-twintail.
The manager requested it.
Like this?
I told my sister this morning that I didn't know what to wear today,
She said, "Why don't you wear this? She said, "Why don't you wear this?
I wore my sister's clothes today. In the morning.
I don't often wear this kind of clothes,
so it's fresh.Fresh.
Today is called finals,
Good night.
I think I'll go to Honey Kitty.
If I'm going to eat, it will be after the concert.
Cookies.
Cute.
There's a memo color.
I got a big fugu-chi daifuku with sushi,
I decided to eat half a hitoka, half a mikan and half a watermelon.
Another haphazare.
The group that got the lunch box!
Yay, yay, yay!
I'll have some Daifuku!
It's not a bento!
This one!
I chose pear!
Rehearsal.
Good morning.
Good morning
Wow.
Oh, my God.
That's amazing.
Three, four, four, five, six.
I see you watching from the store from the store.
Please play the last one, Chose, Micktel.
Please.Please.
Easier to stretch than anyone else.
Cute.
It's nice.
Maybe you can dance anything.
That's good.
Who can dance this best?
This was fun.
It's the 7th.
Yes.
So we're at a four-month standstill.
Four more days.
Let me say hello.
One, two, three, four, five, six.
Dark noves to the hearts of all the staff too!
We are JOLIN.TV.
Please give us your best regards.
Please do.
Thank you for watching.
You live only for me now.
It's okay, number 6, number 1. Please.
It's okay, number 6, man woman. Please.
It's a person who disappears in front of the dressing room.
It's one of the meat buns.
There's a lot of customers coming.
There are customers coming.
They're coming.
Yes, please.
Yes, please.please?
I look forward to working with you.
Yes, ma'am.
Thank you for your time.
I'm here again.
I want to eat Yukiniku bento,
It comes in three halves.
This one has only one piece.
It's like there are 6 winners,
So, it seems like we should all take one.
I didn't read it correctly.
Five cards per person.
Five.
I said five.
Five cards.
I'm sorry.
Five.
Which one do you think I'll win?
This one.
This one?
Okay, you want to start with this one?
Yes, I do.
How many more cards do we have?
Isn't that a pretty good chance?
Yeah, I think so.
It's nice when you get them all.
Wow, you hit them all.
That's the one you're supposed to hit.
I guessed right.I guessed it.
I'm sorry.
Well, let's just say I won.
I'm going to spend the rest of the day with a smile on my face.
Thank you for this wonderful project!
Is it possible that this is thanks to me?
Did I?
Is it?
At the beginning.
You told me that this was a no-brainer.
Is that why you started the project?
I'm glad you did.
I'm going to advertise Cute Memorial.
Cute Memorial is...
Kimi to Seishun is just so good, isn't it?
It's a really great coming-of-age song!
WANTED" is a really nice song.
It's a really nice song.
It tastes like a story!
I'm sorry, I went to the coupling song.
Good night!
Cute Memory" has a really cute choreography,
The choreography of "Cute Memory" is really cute, and recently TikTok has been getting more and more people to use the soundtrack,
I hope you will dance to it too.
The melody is very cute and addictive,
The melody is very cute and addictive, and the song is full of kenken cuteness,
I hope you will listen to it whenever you want to raise your spirits.
That's all for now.
I'm going to eat some sweets at a convenience store now.
Ta-da!ta-da!
Tokyo pigman!
Actually, I just shared one with Hyo Lee.
I'll have another one.
Bon appétit!
Yum!
Delicious!
Mmm...
It feels sweet.
Mmm.
Me too. I think I'm probably going to
Most of the time
I was eating in front of the camera most of the time.
There may have been times when I didn't eat most of it, but I ate most of it.
Please come and see what Takemaru has been up to now.
I'm going to work hard today, and I'm going to use my inhaler again to quench my thirst.
Capion? Capion?
Mommy's doing it.
Capion!
Look, everyone. Here we go.
Yakiniku bento.
Ready.
Ta-da!
Oh no.
It has leeks on it. What should I do?
Let's eat it.
It's an apple this time.
What?
It's nice to meet you.
Are you out today?Are you out today?
Good morning.
Dumpling.
Today, it's kiwi. I had kiwi this morning.
Really?
Kiwi, kiwi, grapes and apples.
And lemon?
Oranges?
Orange.
Can you open it?
Yes, I opened it.
Well, what's this?
I ate it.
The other day, the opening was posted on the fan club's monthly playlist, so please take a look.
There are two more.
Fun!
One hit to the hand,
I can do it.
There are 6 cards in the box.
I hit it.
And I'm going to wave my hand.
I got another one, so that's enough.
Hug.
I'm so happy. I hope I win.
Oh, no. I missed everything.
Oh, no.
Did I miss it?Did it come off?
Oh, it all came off.
Suddenly.
I'll give you four of mine.
Four?
Oh, so that's how it is.
Then, Aki-chan, draw.
Oh, oh, there it is again.
Yay!
Did I hit it?
It's amazing, isn't it? Some of the members didn't hit it.
Even the cucumbers didn't hit it.
What should we do with the cucumbers?
One more.
Is this it?
Is this okay?
I think we're all right.
Aaaaah!
I can't eat my necklace.
Well, then, let's advertise the cute memorial together.
Eat it.
Oh, I'm eating here.
Cute Memorial will be released on September 27.
And it's not a sibling song, but a cup mini song, because it's wonderful even if it's not a sibling song,
There are some songs that I like a lot, like the ones that I can already get into the groove of.
I like it a lot.
It's great, isn't it?
There are songs that make me feel like I'm in a groove, like the ones that people often say are a little disco-ish,
It's a little bit different from your songs and the songs you have done up to now.It's a little different, so Taki's song and also the song up to now.
You said that the songs are from Rolex.
Oh, really?
Suddenly, the part you were singing in the spoiler.
Can I sing it?
So, it's a very youthful song.
I love that one too.
I love that song. I love that song. I was so happy when it came,
I think it's the kind of song that makes you say, "Here it comes!
I'm sure everyone likes it.
I'm really looking forward to singing it live.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'll do my best.
This CD has a lot of contents, so please get it.
Please get it.
This one is cute, too.
When is the Yakiniku Bento coming?
I was in Yakiniku Bento.
Oh, no?
This is the first time.
It's the first time.
What was it?
It was back then. The launch.
It's true. I'm so excited, I'm going to give you the Seiden present.
What'll it be?
What do you want?
I don't know.
I'm kind of looking forward to creating some tension,
What do you think it is?
I think it's a skiing character.I think it's a ski character.
They see it differently. Together.
What do you think?
I'm looking forward to it!
What's that? Huh?
No, no, no, no.
I'm making it smell so good.
I'm sure there will be another one.
Have fun.
Next time, we'll go to your room.
That's sweet.
And you'll watch it in your room?
Yeah, I will.
Bye bye.
Have a nice day. See you again.
So cute!
I just ate a yakiniku bento.
I won.
You won?
I won, too.
Bowman might have won everything.
I'm sure.
Here we go.
And...
Hazlet.
Second one.
Bingo!Bingo!
I get two rounds in a row!
I won!
I won two in a row!
Oh, no!
Sorry!
I won two!
Sorry! I won two!
Oh my God!
But you know, Hiyori hasn't won once yet!
Sorry!
Hello!
Well, read and write!
Ah!
You're right!
But I can't read!
Bingo!
I can't read!
Well then, staff, we'll be waiting for you!
Cute memory album, right?
It has a dialogue part!
The first one is "Cute! and the second part is "Cute!
And number 2 is "Cute!" and the second one is "Cute!
and the third one is a big "Cute!
The third one is a big, stomping, "Cute!
The other feature of the song is a dance in which everyone shakes their hearts together.
And now, it is the theme song of Minato Shoji Laundromat 2,
Everyone danced to it!You all danced too!
So please check out Minato Sho's twitter!
The coupling songs are cute, cool, and fun too!
I think the title of the song has already been released,
Please look forward to it!
That's all!
I'll be waiting!
How many rooms?
Oh! Oh, no!
I feel like I'm growing wings.
Flutter, flutter, flutter, flutter.
Catch me.
I can't wait to see what today's catch will be!
I'm grinning!
Today is the super-tokimeki publicity department
Heart Lock On Hall Lock On
Heart Rock On Hall Tour 2023
You're too cute, too cute, too cute! to
Thank you very much for coming.
Thank you very much!
Yes! This is Hiyori Yoshikawa, aka Hiyori from Super Tokimeki Green!
I'm Hiyori Yoshikawa, a.k.a. "Super Thrilling Green Hiyori", and I'm here to take
Photo shooting in the venue
Lock-on
Video recording is strictly prohibited.
Yes, we do.
Cheering is allowed within the confines of your seat for this performance.
Please wear a non-woven mask when cheering
Sorry! I'm so sorry.
Please be sure to wear a non-woven mask even when cheering!Please be sure to wear a non-woven mask even when speaking out
Yes
There are no restrictions on the volume or duration of vocalizations in your seat.
However, we ask that you do not disturb the performance
or disturb other audience members.
Please refrain from shouting in a manner that may disturb the performance
Excessive jumping is also prohibited.
In case of emergency, please follow the instructions
In case of emergency, please follow the instructions of our staff and evacuate the venue.
In case of emergency, please follow the instructions of our staff and evacuate.
Please.
We ask for your cooperation.
Yes, sir.
The show will begin shortly.
Hello.
I'm Pablin.
I'm Pavlin.
It's Pavlin.
No, that's a fake.
Yoo-hoo!
It's Pavlin.
Everybody, swooper final.
Come on. Come on.
Is everything okay today?
Swooper Finals.
You didn't make it today.
I'll be fine.It's okay. It's okay.
It's okay, I've been played.
The wall of laughter came down.
Okay, I'm going to go play.
Here you go.
Thank you.
Yuriya.
here
Haruko
Autumn
Hiyori
Super Tokimeki Advertising Department
Rock on!
Everyone is in good spirits
Cheerful
Let's have fun!
All right.
It's good.
Good, good, good.
All right.
Oh!
Scary, scary, scary.
Double combo.
Ohkun, ohkun, ohkun...
Okun, okun, okun, okun...
Okun, okun, okun...
Okun, Okun, Okun, Okun...
Ohkun, ohkun, ohkun, ohkun, ohkun...Oh, my God, oh, my God, oh, my God...
Okun, Okun, Okun...
Okun, okun, okun, okun...
Whoo! Whoo-hoo!
Whoo! Hoo-hoo!
Final!
I'm looking forward to it!
I'll do my best!
Whoo!
Go!
Best technique!
Thank you very much.
You all did a great job presenting.
Thank you very much. Thank you very much for your hard work.
It was fun.
It was fun!
What's that? I wonder when the additional show is.
The additional show is in Toyoyama, right?
Toyoyama.
Additional show, Toyoyama, please.
Ishikawa, please.
Ishikawa.
I want to go to Ishikawa.
Hokkaido, please.Hokkaido is also good, please.
Hokkaido is also good.
Okinawa too.
About four more places.
Something like that.
I'll be sad when it's over.
It will be very sad.
It was fun.
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you very much.
It was fun!
It was the most fun!
Um, soooo cute memorial.
He's an amazing dancer, so...
If you want, you can also search for Super Express
If you could check out their YouTube page...
I'd be very happy if you could watch them on YouTube.
I apologize for the inconvenience.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
I'm so happy.
You're singing really well.
Thank you for performing the tour!
Thank you so much!
It's over!
Thank you for all your hard work! Thank you all for your hard work!
Thank you for your hard work!
Bye bye!
Bye bye!Bye bye!
Thank you.
At the end of the tour, the six of us were able to enjoy ourselves safely.
I think the tour was also a great opportunity to meet new publicity members.
Yes, it was.
It was great. We went to many places.
The invitations were fulfilling, weren't they?
Please take a look at everyone's Kakibara that I wanted to look back on.
Look at all of them.
But I'm a little sad. When it's over.
Good.
We'll do our best so that we can go back to see the publicity staff all over the country.
Next up is the one-man live band Kakikuri.
It's going to be Kakikuri again.
I'm looking forward to it.
There's also Yokokaiwari.
Please don't forget this and come visit us.
I'll be waiting for you.
Thank you for the tour.
Thank you for your hard work.
How was it?
I think we had a really fulfilling summer,
Yes, it was.
We were so happy to see that the youth mentors were really happy and enjoying themselves at all the shows,
It made us very happy too,
It was a tour that made us realize how fun it is to perform live.
It was a tour, but each of the 10 shows had its own memories,
It was like an individual live concert, even if it wasn't an all-inclusive tour,
I also felt that I was able to get closer to the young waiters,I thought I got closer to the youth waiters,
We also stayed together with the members this summer.
We stayed together with the members and traveled a lot this summer. We stayed together with the members.
I have good memories of talking with them a lot more.
Moreover, this tour was the first time in a long time that we avoided doing voices,
It had been a long time since everyone and I had been able to be in the audience.
I had always wanted to be in the audience, so I was able to be there, and even the young waiters took a lot of pictures with us, so I have more memories.
I hope you all had a good time.
Will there be another tour next year?
I don't know. I think there will be.
There will be a slow one, a side picture one, and another one in between,
We will all do our best.
Thank you for your continued support.
The finals are over.
It's over. Thank you for your hard work. And everyone.
Thank you all for your hard work.
There were some places that we went to for the first time as a super-time line, and so on,
It was the first time for us to go to some places as Chochi Line, and it was the first time for us to go on tour since the regression of the voice,
I was so happy to hear many calls for the songs after the new year,
I was very happy.
I look back at all 10 stops,
I think that about 20,200 people were involved in this tour,
If you add up the 300 people who were involved in the tour, the staff, and all the other people involved,
I think that many people were really involved in this tour,
I am very happy right now.
It's amazing, isn't it? So many people were involved in this one tour,
I am very grateful that so many people were involved in this one tour.
So, I will do my best to connect this tour horizontally.
We have been to various regions and met with various publicity staff members,
I would like to do my best so that they will come to meet us this time.Now we will try our best to get the publicity staff to come and see us.
We won't have a one-man luncheon for a while,
I think there are probably some of you who can't participate in the one-man-runge for a while, and maybe you can't even participate in the ji-ritsu,
So, I hope we can meet at the sidewalk division,
I hope to see you all at the Yoko-Wari.
I'll be waiting for you.
Good luck tomorrow.
Let's work hard.
Eternal good-bye.
Yukichan Otsukare-sama.
Otsukare-sama.
It's over for 10 minutes.
It's over.
It was really fun,
I even went on the MC,
I didn't really like summer that much.
I always wondered if it was summer,
I spent a lot of time with all the members,
I spent a lot of time with the members, went to many places, and made many happy memories,
I started to like summer,
I felt that summer is really nice and that I like summer,
I think this year has been one of the most positive changes in my life,
I think this year has been a good change in my life.
I am happy.
I am very happy to be able to go to Indonesia in parallel with the tour,
It's amazing to be able to go to Indonesia in parallel with the tour.
It seems like a long time ago, doesn't it?
It was such a fulfilling summer,
I feel like I'm having such a fulfilling summer with AOA,
I am happy.Glad to hear it.
I think. Thank you very much.
Now that September is over,
School has already started for some of you,
I know there are children who have already started school, or who have already started a lot of new things,
I think they will have a lot of difficulties at the beginning of their school year,
I want to be a part of that.
I agree, we are the source of such power.
We will do our best.
I hope we can continue to do so.
I will do my best.
I will never forgive today's affair.
I'm sure you heard that. Everyone.
I hope you guys don't cheat on me.
Because, hey, it's a prelude, right?
I had made sure that I wouldn't cheat on you until then,
I'm sure it'll be fine.
It's perfect, right?
I think it hit a chord.
No cheating!
I'll see you again in a couple of days.
See you soon.
Thanks for your hard work, I enjoyed the 10 shows.
I hope you won't cheat on me in the future.
Don't cheat on me for a minute, forgive me.
I'm sure there is someone crying somewhere.
I'm sure there's someone somewhere getting wet again.
I hope it's not too cold.
I'm sure that somewhere someone is crying
Just a little bit of meJust a little bit of my feelings
I want to share it with you
Still in front of me
I don't even know where I'm going
Come on, let's go wherever you want
Goodbye goodbye, thank you for yesterday
After the rain, the cityscape turns color
On the canvas of my broken heart
Paint a piece of the future
It's leading me to the future
Subtitle: Kyou
Now I can tell you the reason for my tears
When you're lost, just remember
I'll smile even when it's raining
Come on, let's go wherever you want
Goodbye goodbye to yesterday's me
After the rain, the streets are shimmering
It's as if my heart is in a sunny mood
Rainbow pools, rainbow pianos, rainbow pianos, rainbow pianos
Goodbye goodbye to yesterday's me
After the rain, the streets are shimmering
My heart is like a sunny day, spilling clouds of tears
I'll wear a rainbow dress
Goodbye goodbye